We're gonna liberate the sh** out of you.
War Machine is a comedy, drama, war film directed by David Michôd.
A rock star general bent on winning the “impossible” war in Afghanistan
takes us inside the complex machinery of modern war.
Inspired by the true story of General Stanley McChrystal.
Gen. Glen McMahon, played by Brad Pitt.
Greg Pulver, played by Anthony Michael Hall.
Willy Dunne, played by Emory Cohen.
Cory Staggart, played by John Magaro.
Matt Little, played by Topher Grace.
German Politician, played by Tilda Swinton.
War Machine is a 2017 American satirical war comedy film written and directed by David Michôd and starring Brad
Pitt, Anthony Michael Hall, Anthony Hayes, Topher Grace, Will Poulter, Tilda Swinton, and Ben Kingsley.
Based on the nonfiction book The Operators: The Wild and Terrifying Inside Story of America's War in Afghanistan by Michael
Hastings, it is a fictionalized version of the events in the book based on United States Army General Stanley McChrystal.
The film was released on Netflix on May 26, 2017.
The film explores themes of journalist, based on novel or
book, afghanistan, us army, historical fiction.
The tone is lighthearted and emotional and thought_provoking.